Is class okay?
The professor teaches well
Is there any other general education class you’d recommend besides this?
Um... Huh? Ah!
I think the counseling went okay
After this, do you have a free period (class break)?
Yes
Hmm...
What... let’s go to a café...
Want to do our homework together?
Okay
Then
Ah...
Still studying?
Oh, you're doing your homework until so late
You’re craving nicotine
Stop it, will you
It’s going to rot my lungs
What—? I’m not a kid, you know?
Hey, but let’s stop the assignment now and go
grab a drink
Huh?
Hey, we haven't even been working on the assignment for an hour yet
I’m already done
This is a piece of cake
Ah... this is really unfair
So you think Yeongjae is different from that?
Oh, what—just with something like this?
Oh, really! You said your place is around here, right?
Can we go out for fun?
Huh?
Now?
The house is dirty
I don’t mind the child’s situation
Let’s go get some drinks
Hmm...
How about 치맥 (chimaek)?
- This way
Here?
Of course you can’t go without chicken and beer
Since you bought the chicken, you have to eat both of the legs
Yeah, you’re really into junk food, huh?
Yeah
You and I really match well
What taste is there to go with tough meat like that?
Because tough meat is actually much more plain and tastes better, though?
Oh, do you remember the name of that chicken place that was in front of our school?
Oh, what was that name again...?
Hoseok’s chicken!
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah—Hoseok’s chicken
- Oh, we really used to go there all the time
It was really delicious
I can't forget that taste
That sweet and sticky seasoning
Let’s go there once next time
Okay
Not really
I don’t know, but it kind of seems like they might not be open for business
Is that so?
But why haven’t you contacted me even once?
You even changed your number
You can still keep in touch even if you go abroad to study
Did I do something that made you angry?
No, it’s not like that
Then why did you do that?
My parents are really strict
Just pressuring me to go do an MBA
It wasn’t even something I went for willingly to study abroad
I was just feeling a bit overwhelmed
I was wondering—did I do something that upset you?
I was worried about that
Oh!
What? Did you get hurt?
Whether it’s in the past or now,
it’s all the same if you get hurt, right? It’s fine—it's just a slight cut
Saying it’s okay is the same now as it was back then
Come here—about the work
You got badly hurt, didn't you?
- When I… (at that time)
If you kissed
What happened?